Guide to the UE Publications Collection, 1936-1990s UE.8.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE Publications Collection
1936-1990s
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.8.1
68.75 Linear Feet (55 boxes)
The United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) utilized various publications at the national, district, and local levels to disseminate information to its members. This subgroup contains publications created and collected by the UE. Included are informational booklets, shop papers, bulletins, and company newsletters.
Scope and Content Notes
This subgroup contains newspapers, newsletters, booklets, pamphlets, leaflets, and bulletins created by the UE, companies, and other unions regarding local and national labor issues and union organizing. Many company publications are from Westinghouse and General Electric. Topics of interest include Communism, political action, and UE accomplishments. Publications collected by the Research Department have been retained in record group UE 10 Research Department. Organizer's Bulletinscan be found in UE 7-4 UE Organizer's Bulletins.
Arrangement
The entirety of this collection has not been arranged; however, an inventory exists for many of the publications created between 1936 and the 1970s. Please contact the Archives Service Center for more information.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1976, 1986, 1997, and 2004.
Previous Citation
UE Publications Collection, 1936-1990s, UE.8.1, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
UE Organizer's Bulletins 1937-1977, UE.7.4, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Labor; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Publications; Labor unions -- Organizing -- United States -- History; Labor unions -- United States -- History; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
- One Big Industrial Union for the Electrical and Radio Workers of America, March 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- General Electric Company Profits, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Organize Now Regarding General Electric, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Industrial Relations Regarding Business Week, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Know the Truth Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Common Sense Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- For a Stabilized Radio Industry Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- International Association of Oil Field, Gas Well and Refinery Workers of America, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Shop Steward System and Local Union Problems, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Information for Employees Regarding Unemployment Compensation, December 1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Demand for Regulation of Labor Unions, January 15, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- More Facts Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, February 20,1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- United Shoe Workers of America, November 1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Why the Wagner Act Should Not Be Amended, December 1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The People in the United States Regarding Philco Boycott, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Whose Amendments Regarding National Labor Relations Act, May 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- A New Blow at Labor Regarding Hosiery Workers, Sherman Act, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- To the Employees of the General Electric Company Regarding Contract and Organization, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Here's a Little Job for You Regarding International Association of Machinists and Fort Wayne General Electric, January 10, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- CIO's 1940 Legislative Program, January 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- How to Calculate Benefits Under Federal Old-Age and Survivors Insurance, January 1940 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- How a Union Saved 1500 Jobs Regarding Emerson, March 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Secret Ballot Tells the Story Regarding Organization, April 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Your Union at Work, April 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Your Union at Work, Second Edition, May 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Your Union at Work, Third Edition, June 1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Sin of Anti-Semitism, July 1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Anti-War Bibliography, August 1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A Retraction of Dies Committee Charges Against Our Union, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Six Good Reasons Why You Should Vote Yes Regarding Fort Wayne General Electric Organization, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Your Union at Work, Fourth Edition, January 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- The Fight Against Hitlerism, July 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Your Union at Work, Fifth Edition, August 1941 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Your Rights Under the National Labor Relations Act, Third Edition, November 1941 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The Shop Steward System and Local Union Problems, Second Edition, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- How Fascism Thwarts the Life Instinct, April 1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- What Labor is Doing in the War, May 1, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- What Wartime Price Control Means to You, May 1942 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Move and Faster Regarding Productivity Drive, May 1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Move and Faster Regarding Productivity Drive, May 1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Your Union at Work, Seventh Edition, June 1942 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- New York's Wartime Election, September 1942 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- After The War--Toward Security, September 1942 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Your Union at Work, Eighth Edition, November 1942 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Production for Victory, December 1942 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Monopoly in the United States, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- The History of the Shorter Workday, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- The History of the Shorter Workday, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- The High Cost of Living and How to Fight It, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- The Century of the Common Man Regarding Political Action, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Production for Victory - and Your Livelihood, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Economics of the Home Front, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Allied Labor Unity Vital to Victory Now, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Where Can We Get War Workers, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- War Production Plan, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Labor in Australia, March 1943 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- UE Manual on Executive Order 9240 Regarding Overtime, October 8, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- For the Nation's Security Regarding Legislation and Congress of Industrial Organization, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- The Truth About Reader's Digest, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- How Corporations Conceal Profits, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- America and Russia, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- The Tax Bill, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- The Manpower Problem - and You, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- America Must Work Together Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- UE Policy #1 Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Help Lick Fascism Regarding Organization, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- The Wage Policy of the UE, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Good Shelter for Everyone Regarding Housing, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- UE Women Work for Freedom, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Teheran and America Regarding Foreign Policy and Communist Pact, January 1944 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- As WE Win Regarding Reconversion, January 1944 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- War and Post-War Adjustment Policies, February 15, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- War and Post-War Adjustment Policies, February 15, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- UE Under Contract, March 1, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Going Back to Civilian Life Regarding Veterans, March 9, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Information for Workers Regarding Unemployment Compensation, March 1944 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- There is No Substitute Regarding Health Insurance, March 1944 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- UE Guide to Political Action, Second Edition, April 1944 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- UE Guide to Political Action, Second Edition, April 1944 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Soviet Russia and the Post-War World, May 1944 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- UE Under Contract, June 1, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Let's Go to Press, June 1944 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Planning for Jobs Regarding Reconversion and Political Action, July 15, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- The Shop Steward on the Job, July 1944 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- UE Looks at FDR, July 1944 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Lock the Door and Call a Lawyer, July 1944 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- UE Under Contract, September 1, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Why Support Roosevelt, September 2, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Suggested Sample Constitution for UE Locals, September 1944 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- UE 1936-1944, September 1944 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- The Shop Steward on the Job, October 1944 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- When You Come Back, December 1944 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Our Job in the Pacific Regarding Foreign Policy, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- UE Guide to Group Insurance, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Facts and Tips for Service Men and Women, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- The Negro in America, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Organized Labor in the Soviet Union, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- The Baltic Soviet Republics, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- The Truth About Subsidies Regarding Farmers, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Federal Ballot Plan, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Jobs for All After the War, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Your Cost of Living, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- What Is the PAC, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- For American Youth Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Your UE News, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- The People's Program for 1944 Regarding Political Action (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Radio Handbook, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- A Woman's Guide to Political Action, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- WLB Brief, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Constitution of the USSR, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- The Republican Party and US Foreign Policy, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Songs for Political Action, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- PAC Needs, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- The Victory of the American People Regarding Political Action, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- UE Publications, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- UE's No. 1 Campaign Regarding Wages, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Jobs for All Regarding Political Action, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- You and Your Steward, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- You and Your Neighborhood Regarding Planning, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Labor and Education, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Federal Ballot Plan, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- The People Can Win in 1944 Regarding Political Action (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Labor's Political Aims, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Greetings, UE Regarding Organization, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- What Every Canvasser Should Know Regarding Political Action, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- All Men are Neighbors Regarding Political Action, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Every Worker a Voter #1, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Every Worker a Voter #2, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- WLB Brief Regarding UE, General Electric and Westinghouse, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- This Is Your America Regarding Political Action, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Speakers Manual Regarding Political Action, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Declarations of the World Trade Union Conference, February 1945 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- America's Decisive Battle Regarding Communist Party, March 1945 (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Sample Contract, March 1945 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Real Issues Regarding United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, April 23, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- At the World Labor Conference, April 1945 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Good Advice! Regarding No-strike Pledge and Organization, April 1945 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- CIO Veteran`s Guide, April 1945 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Draft Constitution of World Federation of Trade Unions, May 1945 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Sample Ballot Regarding Philadelphia General Electric White Collar, May 23, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- UE Under Contract, June 1, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Unemployment Insurance Information for Employees Regarding New York, June 1945 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Know the Score Regarding National Maritime Union, June 1945 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- The Shop Steward on the Job, June 1945 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- The Road to Tokyo and Beyond Regarding WWII, Reconversion, July 1, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- $1000 Reward Regarding Organization, U.S. Motors and Inter-union Rivalry, July 17, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Race Riots Aren't Necessary, July 1945 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Lift the Lid on Your Salary Freeze, July 1945 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- For the Nation's Security Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizatio and Legislation, August 1945 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Immediate Action Regarding Radio, October 1945 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- The Book the Nazis Like Regarding USSR, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Jews in American History, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Labor's Enemy Anti-Semitism, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- For the People's Health Regarding Health, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Report on World Unity Regarding World Federation of Trade Unions, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 96)
- They Still Carry On Regarding Fascism, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Production Guide Regarding Labor-management and Productivity Committee, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- The Five Points of AWSE Leaders Regarding White Collar Westinghouse Workers, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Farm Machinery Monopoly Firms Regarding United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- A Message Regarding General Electric and Westinghouse Negotiations, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- UE Guide for Servicemen's and Veteran's Welfare Committee, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- The Story of Dumbarton Oaks Regarding United Nations, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- UE Regarding White Collar Workers Organization, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Labor's Political Future in the United States, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Everybody's Business Regarding Foreign Policy, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Housing and Jobs Conference Regarding New York City Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- The People's Plan for Reconversion, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 102)
- Re-employment Regarding Reconversion, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- UE Fights for Job Security, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Report of the CIO Delegation to the Soviet Union, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- The Road to Freedom Regarding Wages, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- The Answer is Full Employment, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 107)
- Let Our People Live Regarding Wages, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 108)
- Soviet Sports, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- An Urgent Message Regarding Westinghosue and White Collar Workers, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 109)
- UE Women Face the Future, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Industrial Unionism Regarding Organization, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- Democracy in the UE Regarding Organization, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- UE-CIO Regarding Wages, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 110)
- An M.V.A. for All Regarding Missouri Valley Authority, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Join UE-CIO To Win a Real Salary Increase Regarding Westinghouse and White Collar, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Your Union Dues Regarding Organization, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Bretton Woods Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization and Economics, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- What UE-CIO Is Doing and Can Do for You Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- Extra Regarding U.S. Motors and MESA Inter-union Rivalry, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 111)
- UE Guide to Unemployment Compensation, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- How the UE Was Formed, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- What, Why, How Regarding General Electric White Collar Workers, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- What Score Do You Have On Regarding Fair Employment Practices Committee, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 112)
- Would You Smile Regarding Blacks, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Security and Jobs For All Regarding Political Action, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Now Regarding Political Action, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 113)
- Support UE Workers in Their Fight for a Living Wage Regarding Westinghouse, General Electric and Genreal Motors Strikes, February 1, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Support UE Workers in Their Fight, Second Edition, February 15, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 114)
- UE Fights For a Better America Regarding 1946 Strike and Record (Box 2, Folder 114)
- Urgent Summons to a Congress on Civil Rights Regarding Congress on Civil Rights, April 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Emspak Open Letter to UE Westinghouse Members Regarding Westinghous Strikes, May 7, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Political Guide Regarding Political Action, June 26, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Your UE News, June 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Stop the Drive to War Regarding Foreign Policy and Political Action, June 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Where Were the AFL Top Officials Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, June 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- Greetings Regarding Membership Drive, June 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- The Pavement Trail Regarding Allis Chalmers Strikes, June 1946 (Box 2, Folder 115)
- A Message to You Regarding Organization, June 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Your Government Says Regarding Organization, June 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- You and Your Steward Regarding Steward System, June 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- These UE-CIO War Veterans Fight for a Better America Regarding Organization, July 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- The Case of the Missing T-Bones Regarding United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America and Prices, July 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- The Secret Ballot Tells the Story Regarding Organization, July 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Your Vote Decides Regarding Political Action, July 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Red Smear, July 1946 (Box 2, Folder 116)
- Your Union at Work Regarding UE, July 1946 (Box 2, Folder 117)
- Workers Prefer UE Regarding Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 1946 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- A Message to Salaried Employees Regarding White Collar and Organizations, July 1946 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Teamwork Among the Unions of the World Regarding World Federation of Trade Unions, August 1946 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- How UE Can Help You Win a More Secure Future Regarding Organization, August 1946 (Box 2, Folder 118)
- Telling the Town Regarding Publicity, August 1946 (Box 2, Folder 119)
- Your Vote Decides, Second Edition Regarding Political Action, August 1946 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- A Message to Western Electric Employees from UE-CIO Regarding Western Electric, August 1946 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- UE-CIO Regarding Membership Drive and Organization and General Electric, September 1946 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- UE-CIO Regarding Membership Drive, Organization and Westinghouse, September 1946 (Box 2, Folder 120)
- Minimum Contract Requirement, September 1946 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Vets Can't Eat Medals Regarding Veterans, October 1946 (Box 2, Folder 121)
- Vets Can't Eat Medals, Small Edition Regarding Veterans, October 1946 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- UE Unites All Workers Regarding Organization, Factionalism and Inter-union Rivalry, October 1946 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- Red Smear Regarding Red-baiting, October 1946 (Box 2, Folder 122)
- The Public Relations Program of the National Association of Manufacturers, October 1946 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- They Were Called Reds Too, November 1946 (Box 2, Folder 123)
- The Secret Ballot Tells the Story Regarding Organization, November 1946 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Sample Constitution Regarding UE, November 1946 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- Why High Food Prices, November 1946 (Box 2, Folder 124)
- UE Women Face the Future, November 1946 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Prices Up, November 1946 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Sample Contract Regarding UE, December 1946 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Who's Got the Money Regarding Organization and Wages, December 1946 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- Why High Food Prices, December 1946 (Box 2, Folder 125)
- How Your Congressman Voted, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 126)
- Tidal Wave Regarding Poetry, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 126)
- Everybody's Business Regarding Discrimination, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 127)
- The Worker and the Law Regarding Legal Advice, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 128)
- Your Civil Rights Regarding Civil Liberties, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 129)
- Report of United States Mediators Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Unfinished Busniess Regarding Political Action, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- What is PAC Regarding Political Action, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Are You a One Arm Batter Regarding Women, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Philip Murray Says Regarding The Truth About Unions, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- Deadline for Action Regarding Films, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 130)
- To Secure the Blessings of Liberty Regarding Civil Liberties, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Source Materials for UE Pamphlet Regarding Job Security, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- FE-CIO Regarding International Harvester Organization and Louisville United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 131)
- Inside Liberated Poland, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 132)
- The Case of the 16 Poles Regarding Poland, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- $27.61 Lost or Stolen Regarding Political Action, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- What Happens to Your PAC Dollar Regarding Political Action, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 133)
- Religion Today in the U.S.S.R., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 134)
- The President's Corner Regarding United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers of America, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- How the American Maritime Workers Are Being Forced to Strike, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- No Homes for the Brave Regarding Housing, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 135)
- A Speaker's Handbook of Facts Regarding Political Action, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 136)
- Religion and Labor, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- The Problem of Franco Spain, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 137)
- What Every Voter Should Know and Do in 1946 Regarding Political Action (Box 2, Folder 138)
- Ten Million of US Regarding Minimum Wage, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- UE Publications, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 138)
- How About a Decent School for Me Regarding Racism, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- We Reaffirm Regarding Factionalism, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Americans Won't Stand for Monopolies Regarding National Association of Manufacturers, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 140)
- How to Organize a Strike Regarding FTA, January 1947 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- 10 to 1 Regarding FTA, January 1947 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Let Them Eat Beans Regarding Prices and Wages, January 1947 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- Who's Got the Money Regarding Wages and Prices, January 1947 (Box 2, Folder 141)
- The Drive Against Labor Regarding Political Action, January 1947 (Box 2, Folder 142)
- 5 Cents a Day Regarding Organization, January 1947 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- Monopoly, March 1947 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- Your UE News, March 1947 (Box 2, Folder 143)
- The Members Run This Union, March 1947 (Box 2, Folder 144)
- The UE Shop Steward, March 1947 (Box 2, Folder 145)
- We Took Our Fight to the People Regarding Phelps-Dodge Strikes, April 1947 (Box 2, Folder 146)
- Prices Would Come Down Regarding Prices, April 1947 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- The UE Record Regarding Taft-Hartley and Red-baiting, April 1947 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- Danger Regarding Taft-Hartley, May 1947 (Box 2, Folder 147)
- How the UE Was Formed Regarding Organization, July 1947 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- UE Means Teamwork Regarding Blacks, July 1947 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Remember Regarding Political Action, August 1947 (Box 2, Folder 148)
- Chug-Chug Regarding Children's Labor Education, September 1947 (Box 2, Folder 149)
- Chug-Chug, Fourth Printing, September 1947 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- Chug-Chug, Fifth Printing, September 1947 (Box 2, Folder 150)
- Chug-Chug, Sixth Printing, September 1947 (Box 2, Folder 151)
- Chug-Chug, Seventh Printing, September 1947 (Box 2, Folder 152)
- Fighting Back with PAC, October 1947 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- You and Your Steward, October 1947 (Box 2, Folder 153)
- Your UE News, October 1947 (Box 2, Folder 153)